Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/chu-nguyen-linh-2088721b2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java Concurrency Multithreading Linux

Chu Nguyen Linh

Software Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced in designing and developing multi-tier web applications using JavaSE, JavaEE and Java

frameworks such as Spring, Hibernate, MyBatis, Apache Kafka. Also proficient in implementing

microservices architecture. Strong experience in Algorithm optimization for improved processing performance and reduce memory consumption in code. Proficient in the Spring Framework ecosystem, including Spring Data JPA, Spring Batch, Spring Security, Experienced in working with various database management systems (DBMS) such as MySQL and Oracle. Familiar with Software Development life cycle (SDLC) and experienced in using different methodologies like waterfall, scrum. Possess knowledge in Cloud (AWS) and capable of building the infrastructure for web application deployed on AWS. Ready to take on difficult challenging task to constantly refresh and improve skills, while contributing to project success.

Experience

Zalo

Senior Software Engineer
June 2024 - Present (10 months)

FPT Software

Java Software Engineer October 2020 - July 2024 (3 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

FPT University

Associate of Science - AS, Computer Software Engineering · (January 2017 - March 2021)